Guide to the Communications Workers of America Records WAG.124
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VIII: Departments/Divisions/Districts, 1937-1991
  - Subseries VIII:A: John Morgan Records, 1961-1977
    - AT&T Study: CWA's "3 Contract Proposal", undated (Box 145, Folder 21)
    - AT&T Study: Discipline, undated (Box 145, Folder 22)
    - AT&T Study: Draft, 1972 (Box 145, Folder 23)
    - AT&T Study: Dress Regulation, 1970-1971 (Box 146, Folder 1)
    - AT&T Study: Drug Program, 1971-1972 (Box 146, Folder 2)
    - AT&T Study: Earnings and Hours (Tables), 1961 (Box 146, Folder 3)
    - AT&T Study: Education Assistance Plan, 1955-1960 (Box 146, Folder 4)
    - AT&T Study: Employee Organizations, 1938 (Box 146, Folder 5)
    - AT&T Study: Equal Employment Opportunity Commission (I), 1971-1972 (Box 146, Folder 6)
    - AT&T Study: Equal Employment Opportunity Commission (II), 1971-1972 (Box 146, Folder 7)
    - AT&T Study: Exit Interviews, 1972 (Box 146, Folder 8)
    - AT&T Study: FCC Investigation of Telephone Industry, 1939 (Box 146, Folder 9)
    - AT&T Study: FCC- Johnson Disqualification, 1968-1970 (Box 146, Folder 10)
    - AT&T Study: Forty-nine Hour Question, 1970-1971 (Box 146, Folder 11)
    - AT&T Study: Grievances, 1955-1971 (Box 146, Folder 12)
    - AT&T Study: Health Insurance, 1964-1965 (Box 146, Folder 13)
    - AT&T Study: Illinois Bell Case, 1968-1970 (Box 146, Folder 14)
    - AT&T Study: Incentive Plan, 1967-1970 (Box 146, Folder 15)
    - AT&T Study: Industrial Evolution, 1966 (Box 146, Folder 16)
    - AT&T Study: Job Application Plan, 1971 (Box 146, Folder 17)
    - AT&T Study: Job Description Study, 1969 (Box 146, Folder 18)
    - AT&T Study: Job Pressures, 1968-1969 (Box 146, Folder 19)
    - AT&T Study: Job Pressures Survey, undated (Box 146, Folder 20)
    - AT&T Study: Labor Relations, 1954-1961 (Box 146, Folder 21)
    - AT&T Study: Labor Relations Manual, 1965-1972 (Box 146, Folder 22)
    - AT&T Study: Long Lines Joint Target Setting, 1972 (Box 146, Folder 23)
    - AT&T Study: Lowenberg Ph D Thesis Notes, undated (Box 146, Folder 24)
    - AT&T Study: Maintenance of Dues, 1966-1969 (Box 146, Folder 25)
    - AT&T Study: Management Problems, 1966-1973 (Box 146, Folder 26)
    - AT&T Study: Maternity, 1965-1971 (Box 146, Folder 27)
    - AT&T Study: Meetings with Management (Districts), 1961-1966 (Box 146, Folder 28)
    - AT&T Study: Member Discontent, 1966-1970 (Box 146, Folder 29)
    - AT&T Study: Miscellaneous Background Material, 1965-1972 (Box 146, Folder 30)
    - AT&T Study: Moonlighting, undated (Box 146, Folder 31)
    - AT&T Study: Nathan Reports, 1965-1969 (Box 146, Folder 32)
    - AT&T Study: Nation's Business Article, 1969 (Box 146, Folder 33)
    - AT&T Study: New York City Strike, 1971 (Box 146, Folder 34)
    - AT&T Study: NY Telephone Promotions Guidelines, 1972 (Box 147, Folder 1)
    - AT&T Study: NLRB Election; Western Electric, Baltimore, 1963 (Box 147, Folder 2)
    - AT&T Study: NLRB; Western Electric Blue Cross, 1964-1968 (Box 147, Folder 3)
    - AT&T Study: Orientation and Induction, 1964-1970 (Box 147, Folder 4)
    - AT&T Study: Overtime, 1964 (Box 147, Folder 5)
    - AT&T Study: Pay Board, 1971-1972 (Box 147, Folder 6)
    - AT&T Study: Pensions, 1968-1973 (Box 147, Folder 7)
    - AT&T Study: Performance Appraisal Program, 1964-1971 (Box 147, Folder 8)
    - AT&T Study: Personal Assessment, 1961-1972 (Box 147, Folder 9)
    - AT&T Studies: Personnel Policies, 1965-1972 (Box 147, Folder 10)
    - AT&T Studies: Physical Fitness Program, 1963-1970 (Box 147, Folder 11)
    - AT&T Study: Pollution, undated (Box 147, Folder 12)
    - AT&T Study: Preliminary Report, 1972 (Box 147, Folder 13)
    - AT&T Study: Racial Discrimination, 1965-1970 (Box 147, Folder 14)
    - AT&T Study: Reactions, 1972 (Box 147, Folder 15)
    - AT&T Study: Recruiting, 1965 (Box 147, Folder 16)
    - AT&T Study: "Responsible Relationship" Clause, 1966-1972 (Box 147, Folder 17)
    - AT&T Study: Right to Work, 1955-1965 (Box 147, Folder 18)
    - AT&T Study: Right to Work, 1966-1972 (Box 147, Folder 19)
    - AT&T Study: Safety, Manholes, 1971 (Box 147, Folder 20)
    - AT&T Study: Savings Plan, undated (Box 147, Folder 21)
    - AT&T Study: Savings Plan, 1969 (Box 148, Folder 1)
    - AT&T Study: Savings Plan, 1970-1975 (Box 148, Folder 2)
    - AT&T Study: Senate Investigation; CWA Exhibits, 1949-1950 (Box 148, Folder 3)
    - AT&T Study: Senate Subcommittee Investigation (I), 1972 (Box 148, Folder 4)
    - AT&T Study: Senate Subcommittee Investigation (II), 1972 (Box 148, Folder 5)
    - AT&T Study: Senate Subcommittee on Labor-Management Relations, 1950-1951 (Box 148, Folder 6)
    - AT&T Study: Sex Discrimination (I), 1972 (Box 148, Folder 7)
    - AT&T Study: Sex Discrimination (II), 1972 (Box 148, Folder 8)
    - AT&T Study: Single Visit Program, 1971-1972 (Box 148, Folder 9)
    - AT&T Study: Supervisors' Manuals, undated (Box 148, Folder 10)
    - AT&T Study: Southern Bell Bargaining, 1950-1959 (Box 148, Folder 11)
    - AT&T Study: Southern Bell Bargaining, 1960-1971 (Box 148, Folder 12)
    - AT&T Study: Strikes (List), 1946-1959 (Box 148, Folder 13)
    - AT&T Study: "Supermarket" Phone Sales, 1970-1972 (Box 148, Folder 14)
    - AT&T Study: Stock Purchase Plan, 1951-1962 (Box 148, Folder 15)
    - AT&T Study: Transfer, 1965-1970 (Box 148, Folder 16)
    - AT&T Study: Unilateral Company Action, 1970 (Box 148, Folder 17)
    - AT&T Study: Unit Bargaining, 1960-1970 (Box 148, Folder 18)
    - AT&T Study: Work Assignment Changes, 1962-1972 (Box 148, Folder 19)
  - Subseries VIII:B: CWA Organizing: James A. Beirne's Records, 1944-1974
    - NFTW: Kearny NLRB Case; NFTW: Organizing W.E. Kearny, NJ Plant-NLBR Case; W.E., 1944-1945 (Box 149, Folder 1)
    - NFTW: Kearny Case Before NLRB Regarding UE-CIO vs. W.E. Co., 1945 (Box 149, Folder 2)
    - Kearny, N.J. (District 1), 1946-1947 (Box 149, Folder 3)
    - Kearny, N.J. (District 1), 1949-1951 (Box 149, Folder 4)
    - Kearny, N.J. Project XVIII (B), (District 1), 1947-1949 (Box 149, Folder 4a)
    - Long Lines National Unit; AUTW Project I, 1946-1947 (Box 149, Folder 5)
    - Sales Unit, TWOC-CIO Sales Local, 1946-1948 (Box 149, Folder 6)
    - NFTW Organizing: External Work-Jurisdiction-Disputes with IBEW, 1946-1947 (Box 149, Folder 7)
    - Work Jurisdiction Disputes, TWOC-IBEW, 1947 (Box 149, Folder 8)
    - Work Jurisdiction Matters; Report of Work Jurisdiction Committee, 1947-1948 (Box 149, Folder 9)
    - Long Lines National Unit, TWOC-Project I-CIO, 1947-1949 (Box 149, Folder 10)
    - Boston Long Lines Project I, 1947-1948 (Box 149, Folder 11)
    - General Project 23: Petry & Crull-Organizing-TWOC, 1947-1948 (Box 149, Folder 12)
    - NFTW Organizing: West Coast Report, 1947 (Box 149, Folder 13)
    - Flyers-West Coast Organizations, 1947-1949 (Box 149, Folder 14)
    - NFTW & CWA Membership Development, 1947-1956 (Box 149, Folder 15)
    - CIO Charter Certificate of Affiliation, 1949 (Box 149, Folder 16)
    - The Beacon, 1948 (Box 149, Folder 17)
    - NABET, 1946-1951 (Box 149, Folder 18)
    - ACEW (Installation) TWOC-CIO, Project III, 1947-1948 (Box 149, Folder 19)
    - Membership Development Charts, Reports, Correspondence, 1947-1956 (Box 149, Folder 20)
    - General-Membership Drives & Reports, TWOC, 1948-1951 (Box 149, Folder 21)
    - General Reports from Crull, Moran & Petry, 1949-1952 (Box 149, Folder 22)
    - Western Union, 1949-1954 (Box 149, Folder 23)
    - Membership Development, 1951 (Box 149, Folder 24)
    - General Correspondence, 1951 (Box 149, Folder 25)
    - Pamphlets, 1951-1953 (Box 149, Folder 26)
    - W.E. Clerical Workers Sales National Unit, 1951-1952 (Box 149, Folder 27)
    - General Correspondence, 1952-1954 (Box 149, Folder 28)
    - J. J. Moran Reports, 1953-1958 (Box 149, Folder 29)
    - CWA Organizing Conference, Mar 7, 1954-Mar 9, 1954 (Box 149, Folder 30)
    - CWA Organizing: General, 1955-1963 (Box 149, Folder 31)
    - Material for staff meetings (District 9), 1958 (Box 149, Folder 32)
    - New Construction-Bell System, AC&R and RCH, 1961-1962 (Box 150, Folder 1)
    - Work Jurisdiction-Internal, 1961 (Box 150, Folder 2)
    - Staff Committee Report on Internal Organizing Program, 1961 (Box 150, Folder 3)
    - Budget Info., 1960-1963 (Box 150, Folder 4)
    - Membership Development, 1963 (Box 150, Folder 5)
    - Local Problems; Wayne K. Hazen Correspondence, 1963 (Box 150, Folder 6)
    - White Collar Workers, 1964-1966 (Box 150, Folder 7)
    - Triple Threat Program (CSC-PR-Org.), 1964 (Box 150, Folder 8)
    - Growth Res. #1-Classical and Non-Classical, 1965 (Box 150, Folder 9)
    - Week-Long Schools; Outlines, 1965 (Box 150, Folder 10)
    - Costs and Projects- External, 1965 (Box 150, Folder 11)
    - Triple Threat-Growth Resolution # 1, 1965 (Box 150, Folder 12)
    - Growth Meeting with staff, 1965 (Box 150, Folder 13)
    - Growth Resolution- Ten Best Organizers, 1965 (Box 150, Folder 14)
    - Materials for Meetings on Organizing, 1965-1966 (Box 150, Folder 15)
    - Growth: General Correspondence; Reports; Newsletters, 1965-1966 (Box 150, Folder 16)
    - Growth: Resolution # 1, 1965-1966 (Box 150, Folder 17)
    - Growth: BAHR/WEst Report on Organizing Study, 1966 (Box 150, Folder 18)
    - W.E. Plant-Shreveport, LA Dispute IBEW (Flyers), 1965 (Box 151, Folder 1)
    - W.E. Plant; Jurisdictional Dispute IBEW-Correspondence, 1965 (Box 151, Folder 2)
    - Contracting Out of Work; Convention Resolution, 1966 (Box 151, Folder 3)
    - Contracting Out of Work and Contracting Work Committee, 1965 (Box 151, Folder 4)
    - Union and District Membership Counts, 1964-1971 (Box 151, Folder 5)
    - Local 4400 Internal Correspondence with International, 1965-1966 (Box 151, Folder 6)
    - Material for Growth Meetings in Districts, 1965-1972 (Box 151, Folder 7)
    - Local Inventory Form, 1966 (Box 151, Folder 8)
    - Bargaining Units; Type of Work Performed and Potentials, 1966 (Box 151, Folder 9)
    - Financial Review of Locals' Cash-Assets, 1966 (Box 151, Folder 10)
    - (District 1-9); Canada, 1966 (Box 151, Folder 11)
    - Growth Analysis (Districts 1-9) and Canada, 1966 (Box 151, Folder 12)
    - Independent Unions, 1966-1967 (Box 151, Folder 13)
    - Service to National Units, 1967 (Box 151, Folder 14)
    - Growth and Administration, 1967 (Box 151, Folder 15)
    - Staff Not Assigned to Locals, 1968 (Box 151, Folder 16)
    - Programs for 100 or More Non-Members, 1968 (Box 151, Folder 17)
    - Growth-Material for District Meetings, 1968 (Box 151, Folder 18)
    - Growth, 1968-1969 (Box 151, Folder 19)
    - Membership Count and Organizing Projects, 1969-1971 (Box 151, Folder 20)
    - External, 1969-1973 (Box 151, Folder 21)
    - Internal and External, 1970-1971 (Box 151, Folder 22)
    - Study of an NLRB Election at Western Electric Plant, 1972 (Box 151, Folder 23)
    - Staff Assigned to Locals, 1971 (Box 151, Folder 24)
    - External Policies and Practices, 1972 (Box 151, Folder 25)
    - District 1, NJ Commercial Project IX (B), 1947 (Box 152, Folder 1)
    - District 1, Division #64 Project NJ, 1947-1948 (Box 152, Folder 2)
    - District 1, NJ Plant-Project IX (A), 1948 (Box 152, Folder 3)
    - Loss of NJ Accounting Division #64; NLRB Election, 1944 (Box 152, Folder 4)
    - District 1, New York Telephone Co., 1949-1959 (Box 152, Folder 5)
    - District 1, New York Downstate-Project X (A), 1947-1949 (Box 152, Folder 6)
    - NY Telephone's Problems with Running Ads, 1959-1960 (Box 152, Folder 7)
    - District 1, New York, 1958-1959 (Box 152, Folder 8)
    - NYC Government Employees, 1965 (Box 152, Folder 9)
    - District 1, Commercial Telegraphers Union, 1966 (Box 152, Folder 10)
    - District 1, Rochester Traffic-Project XIX (A), 1947 (Box 152, Folder 11)
    - District 1, Genesee Valley Telephone Union, 1947 (Box 152, Folder 12)
    - District 1, Upstate New York (All Depts.), 1947-1948 (Box 152, Folder 13)
    - Buffalo Division #'s, UE-CIO Raiding, 1948-1949 (Box 152, Folder 14)
    - District 1, Upstate New York, 1949-1954 (Box 152, Folder 15)
    - W.E.-Buffalo-TWOC-CIO-Raiding, 1948 (Box 152, Folder 16)
    - NY Plant Numbers; Alliance & Connecticut Unions, 1969 (Box 152, Folder 17)
    - District 1, New England; Project XII (A), 1947 (Box 152, Folder 18)
    - District 1, Connecticut Project (XI), 1947-1949 (Box 152, Folder 19)
    - District 1, New England, 1949-1951 (Box 152, Folder 20)
    - District 1, NJ-Project, 1953 (Box 152, Folder 21)
    - General Correspondence, 1947 (Box 152, Folder 22)
    - District 2, Project VI (General), 1947-1948 (Box 152, Folder 23)
    - District 2, Accounting-Project VI (A), 1947-1948 (Box 152, Folder 24)
    - Maryland Telephone Traffic Unions, 1946-1948 (Box 152, Folder 25)
    - District 2, Maryland Plant and Traffic, 1947-1948 (Box 152, Folder 26)
    - District 2, Pennsylvania Traffic-Project VI-D, 1947-1948 (Box 152, Folder 27)
    - District 2, Home Telephone and Telephone Company, 1947 (Box 152, Folder 28)
    - District 2, Pennsylvania Project VI (B), 1947 (Box 152, Folder 29)
    - District 2, Delaware Plant-Project VIII, 1947 (Box 152, Folder 30)
    - District 2, W. E. Allentown Project XVIII, 1947-1949 (Box 152, Folder 31)
    - District 2, W. E. Allentown, PA, 1949 (Box 152, Folder 32)
    - District 2, Pennsylvania-Plant VI (C), 1948-1949 (Box 152, Folder 33)
    - District 2, West Virginia Project XXIV, 1947-1949 (Box 152, Folder 34)
    - District 2, Maryland Project VII (B), 1947-1948 (Box 152, Folder 35)
    - CWA Organizing & Bargaining: District 2, MD Clerical Division #16, 1947-1949 (Box 152, Folder 36)
    - District 2, District 50, UMWA, Baltimore, MD, 1949 (Box 152, Folder 37)
    - District 2, Delaware, 1950 (Box 152, Folder 38)
    - District 2, Federation of Telephone Workers of P.A., 1949-1951 (Box 152, Folder 39)
    - District 2, W.E. Point Breeze, 1947-1951 (Box 152, Folder 40)
    - District 2, Pennsylvania, 1949-1952 (Box 152, Folder 41)
    - District 2, Pennsylvania, 1958 (Box 152, Folder 42)
    - District 2, Electro-Therm-Inc., Laurel, MD, 1963-1964 (Box 152, Folder 43)
    - Quayle Study of NLRB-Election at W.E. Point Breeze Plant, 1963 (Box 152, Folder 44)
    - W.E. Baltimore Works, 1965 (Box 152, Folder 45)
    - Project Report (I. Pilot Location...II) W.E. Bact. III, 1966 (Box 152, Folder 46)
    - Point Breeze (Baltimore, MD), 1966 (Box 152, Folder 47)
    - District 2, Winston-Salem-NC, 1949-1951 (Box 152, Folder 48)
    - Szabo Food, Winston-Salem, NC, 1966 (Box 152, Folder 49)
    - District 2, Telephone Foremen and Engineers, 1947-1948 (Box 152, Folder 50)
    - District 4, Michigan Commercial Project XVI, 1947 (Box 152, Folder 51)
    - District 4, Michigan Accounting Election, 1947 (Box 152, Folder 52)
    - TWOC-CIO-Raiding in Michigan Traffic, 1947-1948 (Box 152, Folder 53)
    - District 4, Ohio Federation-Project V(A), 1947-1949 (Box 152, Folder 54)
    - District 4, Ohio, 1951 (Box 152, Folder 55)
    - District 4, Southwest Ohio Traffic-Project V-c, 1949 (Box 152, Folder 56)
    - District 4, Southwest Ohio Plant Ohio-Project V-(B), 1947-1949 (Box 152, Folder 57)
    - District 5, Illinois Chicago Traffic, Project IV (o), 1947-1948 (Box 152, Folder 58)
    - District 5, Illinois Accounting-IV(A), 1947-1948 (Box 152, Folder 59)
    - Western Electric Project XVIII, 1948 (Box 152, Folder 60)
    - NFTW Organizing: Illinois Telephone Traffic Union, 1947 (Box 152, Folder 61)
    - Illinois Local Traffic Operators, 1950-1951 (Box 152, Folder 62)
    - District 5, Indiana Commercial, 1948 (Box 152, Folder 63)
    - District 5, W.E. Indianapolis, IN, 1948 (Box 152, Folder 64)
    - District 5, Indiana Commercial-XIV(A), 1947 (Box 152, Folder 65)
    - District 5, Indiana Accounting Project XXII, 1947 (Box 152, Folder 66)
    - District 5, Wisconsin Accounting & Project XIII (A), 1947 (Box 152, Folder 67)
    - District 5, W.E. Indianapolis, IN, 1949-1952 (Box 152, Folder 68)
    - District 5, W.E. Hawthorne, IL, 1952 (Box 152, Folder 69)
    - Reports of Mamie Mallowe's Activities, 1953-1954 (Box 152, Folder 70)
    - District 6, Western Electric; Vouchering for George Strick, 1959-1960 (Box 152, Folder 71)
    - District 7, General Engineers, 1947-1948 (Box 152, Folder 72)
    - District 7, W. E. Duluth-Project XVIII, 1947-1948 (Box 152, Folder 73)
    - District 7, W.E., St. Paul-Project XVIII (D), 1947, 1949 (Box 152, Folder 74)
    - District 7, Lincoln Clerical Workers, Div.62, 1948 (Box 152, Folder 75)
    - St. Paul & Duluth, Minnesota, 1949-1951 (Box 152, Folder 76)
    - District 7, Northwestern Area IBEW Road Show, 1952 (Box 152, Folder 77)
    - District 8, Mountain States Accounting and Commercial Project XV, 1947 (Box 152, Folder 78)
    - District 8, Montana-Project XVII, 1947-1948 (Box 152, Folder 79)
    - District 9, West Coast Project III, 1948-1949 (Box 152, Folder 80)
    - District 9, ORTT, 1949-1951 (Box 152, Folder 81)
    - District 9, 1961 (Box 152, Folder 82)
    - District 9, Federation of Women Telephone Workers of Southern California, 1974 (Box 152, Folder 83)
    - Canadian Telephone Employees Assoc., 1950 (Box 152, Folder 84)
    - Canada, Saskatchewan, 1949-1950 (Box 152, Folder 85)
    - Canada General, 1948-1953 (Box 152, Folder 86)
    - Ontario-Quebec, 1951 (Box 152, Folder 87)
    - Federation of Telephone Workers of BC, 1948-1951 (Box 152, Folder 88)
    - British Columbia- Project XX, 1947-1949 (Box 152, Folder 89)
    - Employees of Canadian Independent Telephone Company, 1943 (Box 152, Folder 90)
    - British Colombia, 1948-1951 (Box 152, Folder 91)
    - Weirton Steel (Re-Print), 1944 (Box 153, Folder 1)
    - Kearny: NLRB Brief for Respondent; Western Electric (U.E. v. W.E.), 1945 (Box 153, Folder 2)
    - District 1 Organizing: Kearny Flyers; Newsletters, 1947 (Box 153, Folder 3)
    - District 2 Organizing: Maryland Project VII (B) - Newsletters, 1947-1948 (Box 153, Folder 4)
    - District 2 Organizing: Western Electric, Project XVIII, 1947-1949 (Box 153, Folder 5)
    - CWA Organizing: Rising Prices & Inflation, 1947-1959 (Box 153, Folder 6)
    - Kearny: Western Electric; "The Beacon"; WEEA News; Flyers, 1948 (Box 153, Folder 7)
    - District 2 Newsletter: "The Beacon", 1948 (Box 153, Folder 8)
    - Newsletter: "The Telephone Flash", Oct 1948 (Box 153, Folder 9)
    - District 2 Organizing: Flyers, 1949 (Box 153, Folder 10)
    - District 2 Newsletters/Anti-UE: "The Eye Opener"; Flyers, 1949 (Box 153, Folder 11)
    - District 2 Organizing: Western Electric; Flyers, 1949 (Box 153, Folder 12)
    - Illinois Bell: NLRB Election, CWA & IBEW, 1951-1952 (Box 153, Folder 13)
    - Illinois Bell: NLRB Election, CWA & IBEW, 1951-1953 (Box 153, Folder 14)
    - Organizing Pamphlets, 1951-1954 (Box 153, Folder 15)
    - Materials for Two-Day Educational Institute Program, 1953-1954 (Box 153, Folder 16)
    - CWA Organizing: Labor Movement; Cornell University Conference, 1960-1961 (Box 153, Folder 17)
    - CWA Organizing: Studies on The Decline of the Labor Movement, 1961 (Box 153, Folder 18)
    - CWA Organizing: General Economics, 1962-1976 (Box 153, Folder 19)
    - District 2 Organizing: Electro-Therm & Bendix (NLRB), 1963-1964 (Box 153, Folder 20)
    - Bell System Report: Organizing White Collar Workers, 1964 (Box 153, Folder 21)
    - Triple Threat Program: CSR-PR Organizing, 1964 (Box 153, Folder 22)
    - Organizing: Western Electric Plant (CWA v. IBEW), 1965 (Box 153, Folder 23)
    - Western Union Organizing Campaign (Wage Re-Opener), 1966 (Box 153, Folder 24)
    - CWA Organizing: "Labor's Role in America", Letter to CWA Members, 1965 (Box 153, Folder 25)
    - CWA Organizing: "Labor's Role in America", Letters to Industrial Leaders & Responses, 1965-1966 (Box 153, Folder 26)
    - CWA Organizing: "Labor's Role in America", 1965 (Box 153, Folder 27)
    - CWA Organizing: "Labor's Role in America", Letter to Academics & Responses, 1965 (Box 153, Folder 28)
    - CWA Organizing: "Labor's Role in America", Letter to Educators & Responses 1966 (Box 153, Folder 29)
    - Materials for Meetings on Organizing, 1965-1966 (Box 153, Folder 30)
    - Organizing: Material for Growth in Districts, 1965-1967, 1971-1972 (Box 153, Folder 31)
    - CWA Organizing: Ten Leading National Problems, 1968-1969 (Box 153, Folder 32)
    - Organizing: Report, 1972 (Box 153, Folder 33)
    - CWA Organizing: Multi-National Corporations Study by D&R Dept., 1973 (Box 153, Folder 34)
    - Labor's Role in America: Pamphlets, undated (Box 153, Folder 35)
    - Labor's Role: Business Responses, undated (Box 153, Folder 36)
    - Flyers: Atlanta, 1971, 1972 (Box 154, Folder 1)
    - Phoenix Campaign: Campaign Materials and IBEW; Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 154, Folder 2)
    - Phoenix Campaign: Newsletter; Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 154, Folder 3)
    - CWA Correspondence in re Western Electric Organizing, 1965-1967 (Box 154, Folder 4)
    - Project 345: Shreveport, LA, 1965 (Box 154, Folder 5)
    - Project 345: Shreveport, LA, 1965 (Box 154, Folder 6)
    - CWA Correspondence; IBEW Election Materials; News Clips, 1965-1968 (Box 154, Folder 7)
    - General Agreement: Western Electric & IBEW - Denver CO, 1970 (Box 154, Folder 8)
    - CWA Election Materials; Correspondence, 1967 (Box 154, Folder 9)
    - CWA Correspondence in re Organizing Western Electric, 1965-1967 (Box 154, Folder 10)
    - Campaign Materials; Flyers, 1971 (Box 154, Folder 11)
    - Denver Campaign: 1st Contract, 1969-1970 (Box 154, Folder 12)
    - CWA Dispute with IBEW: Western Electric NLRB Hearings, 1965-1968 (Box 154, Folder 13)
    - Jurisdictional Dispute: Graphics, 1966-1968 (Box 154, Folder 14)
    - General Agreement Between W.E. and IBEW, Local 2188, Feb 22, 1966 (Box 154, Folder 15)
    - W.E. CWA Organizing Budget, Jul 1967 (Box 154, Folder 16)
    - CWA Staff: Weekly Activity Reports, Aug 5, 1967-Sep 23, 1967 (Box 154, Folder 17)
    - Arbitration: Speech by Robert Levitt; W.E., Nov 1967 (Box 154, Folder 18)
    - W.E. Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 154, Folder 19)
    - NLRB Hearings in re W.E. & CWA/IBEW Dispute, Jan 1968 (Box 154, Folder 20)
    - Arbitration Decision: W.E., North Carolina & CWA, 1969 (Box 154, Folder 21)
    - NLRB Petitioner's Brief to Regional Director Seeking Election, 1970 (Box 154, Folder 22)
    - Arbitration Decision: Kansas City Works & Local 6360, 1970 (Box 154, Folder 23)
    - CWA Organizing Campaign v. IBEW Correspondence, 1969-1971 (Box 154, Folder 24)
    - IBEW Organizing Campaign Material, 1970 (Box 154, Folder 25)
    - CWA Organizing Campaign Materials v. IBEW, 1969-1970 (Box 154, Folder 26)
    - CWA Campaign v. IBEW Brochures, Flyers, 1970 (Box 154, Folder 27)
    - IBEW Organizing Campaign Material v. CWA, 1971 (Box 154, Folder 28)
    - CWA Organizing Campaign Materials v. IBEW Flyers; Newsletters, 1971 (Box 154, Folder 29)
    - NLRB: Unfair Labor Practice, W.E. Installation (Christy P. Nicholas) IBT, 1962 (Box 155, Folder 1)
    - Morton Bahr Notebook, 1963 (Box 155, Folder 2)
    - Telephone Campaign, 1963 (Box 155, Folder 3)
    - CWA Mail-Outs: Correspondence, 1963 (Box 155, Folder 4)
    - BTW Mail-Outs, 1963 (Box 155, Folder 5)
    - IBT Mail-Outs, undated (Box 155, Folder 6)
    - CWA Mail-Outs: Local 1101, undated (Box 155, Folder 7)
    - CWA Handbills, 1963, 1964 (Box 155, Folder 8)
    - BTW Handbills/Coloring Book & BTW Membership Card, 1963 (Box 155, Folder 9)
    - CWA News, Sep 1963-Feb 1964, 1964 (Box 155, Folder 10)
    - Local 1101 Handbills, 1963 (Box 155, Folder 11)
    - Local 1103 Handbills, 1962 (Box 155, Folder 12)
    - Teamster Meetings, Dec 1963 (Box 155, Folder 13)
    - Local 1101, 1963, 1964 (Box 155, Folder 14)
    - IBT Handbills, 1963-1964 (Box 155, Folder 15)
    - The Crusader (Newspaper): IBT Election Issue, 1964 (Box 155, Folder 16)